kryptoads.com 2019-02-25

# KryptoAds: CPM Advertising Network

**Privacy statement (updated 25th May 2018)**   
Our data privacy statement, sets out how we handle personal data. We are aware of the importance to users of how personal data are handled and we assure you that we observe all relevant legal requirements. We consider the protection of your privacy to be of paramount importance. For this reason, compliance with the legal requirements on data privacy is, for us, a matter of course.  
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to a change in legal, technical or business developments. Changes will be posted on our Websites and the effective date of the Privacy Policy will be revised accordingly. 

**Contact and data protection commissioner**   
Ad Center Srls, Street C. Battisti 21, 20037 Paderno Dugnano, Italy  
You can contact our data protection officer(s) at info@kryptoads.com 

**Informations we collect**   
Certain parts of our website may ask you to provide us with personal information about you voluntarily. For example, we may ask you to provide your contact details (such as your name, email address and phone number) when you: register an account with us or submit enquiries to us.The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.   
We use cookies and IP locating technology through our ad exchange platform. With the help of this informations, users will see advertisements customized to their country, device, browser and OS. Some of this information, for example your IP addresses and certain unique device identifiers, may identify a particular computer or device, and may therefore be considered “personal data” in some jurisdictions in the European Economic Area and elsewhere. Some of this information may be collected using cookies and similar tracking technology, as explained further. 

**How we handle informations?**   
We use informations provided in registration form for the login, for updating informations and for financial purpose. Data collected via the Ad Exchange are used for optimizing needs of advertisers’ campaigns, making the campaigns to better meet their objectives. Advertisers may use the platform data i.e.:   
for Category-based advertising   
to limit the amount of impressions per user per day   
to show particular ads to particular locations   
to place offers related to the content of the web page on which they are shown   
to determine how users respond to an ad.   
With the help of our report buyers learn about the effectiveness of their online ads. Our Exchange uses platform data for cross-device mapping in order to serve or measure ads on related devices on behalf of our clients. 

**Cookies**  
Like most Internet sites, we and our ad serving party use "cookies" to enhance the Internet user's experience on the Web. Neither we nor such third party ad serving party uses these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files.  
A cookie is a unique number that is assigned to you the first time you are served an ad. This number is stored in a file on your computer. For instance, cookies help ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same ad.   
Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site and the effectiveness of an ad. This information can then be used by advertisers to better cater to your needs. In other words, cookies help us deliver to you the types of ads in which you are more interested.  
Although we believe that cookies help enhance your experience on the Web we or our third ad serving party do not need cookies to deliver ads to you.   
If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, you may either manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser, or you can opt out reading informations contained in the following link [https://www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) or you may [click here](https://p.ato.mx/optout?out=1) to prevent our cookies from being stored on your browser. 

**Legal basis**  
Your data are handled according to the following legal provisions:   
with regard to data communicated in forms, etc. with your consent, Art. 6(1) (a) GDPR   
with regard to services you use for the performance of a contract, Art. 6(1)(b) GDPR   
otherwise, with particular regard to statistical data and online identifiers based on legitimate interests, Art 6(1)(f) GDPR 

**Retention period**  
Personal data will only be collected by us to the extent and for the purpose for which you provide the data to us, e.g. for registration or for distributing ads. We retain your data untill you write us to delete you. 

**Data protection**  
We have taken extensive technical and organisational measures to secure your data against potential risks, such as unauthorised login or access, unauthorised perusal, amendment or distribution, as well as against loss, deletion or misuse. In order to protect your personal data against unauthorised access by third parties when being transmitted, we secure data transmissions, if necessary, using SSL encryption. This is a standard encryption procedure for online services, particularly for the Internet.
